Guide to the Bryant Fleming plans, [ca. 1904-1937]
Fleming, Bryant plans
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Bryant Fleming plans, [ca. 1904-1937]
1380
Fleming, Bryant,
27 cubic ft., 54 mapcase folders
Building plans
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Sketches, plans, details, and blueprints of landscaping projects for parks, private estates, and housing projects from Fleming's landscape architecture firms.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Landscape architect.
Bryant Fleming received a B.S. from Cornell University in 1901. He formed Townsend & Fleming in Buffalo, New York (1905), and dissolved the partnership in 1915 when he established an independent practice in Wyoming, New York. He moved his office to Ithaca in 1927, where he continued his practice until retirement in the late 1930s. Fleming taught as a visiting professor at Cornell, and he helped develop the Department of Landscape Architecture. He was also involved in campus planning at Cornell and was an active member of the American Society of Landscape Architects' Committee on Education.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Sketches, plans, details, and blueprints of landscaping projects for parks, private estates, and housing projects from Fleming's landscape architecture firms. Includes working papers of buildings by various architects, including the Avery Coonley Estate in Illinois by Frank Lloyd Wright.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Fleming, Bryant, 1877-1946.; Wright, Frank Lloyd, 1867-1959.; Townsend & Fleming.
Subjects:
Architecture.; Coonley, Avery House (Riverside, Ill.); Landscape architecture.
Form and Genre Terms:
Architectural drawings.; Blueprints.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
SERIES LIST
Series I. Clients A-H
Series II. Clients J-P
Series II. Clients P-Y
Series III. Unidentified Clients - In Sheet Number Order
CONTAINER LIST
- Link to a copy of the printed finding aid. 22MB PDF file
  This is most helpful if you want the list by plan number. Please check back to online finding aid for the most accurate location information.
  Contents
  List of drawings by geographic location - Pages 3-9
  List of drawings by last name of client (sheet numbers grouped) - Pages 10-16
  List of drawings by last name of client (each sheet number listed individually) - Pages 17-35
  List of drawings by sheet number - Pages 36-74
  Handwritten list of drawings - Pages 75-131
  Additional lists and indices - Pages 132-143
- Series I. Clients A-H
  - Acer, John H.
    Montreal, Province du Québec
    - Bird's eye view showing garden, Undated; Sheet # 103 (Box 6)
      Sheet # 103
      Scale: Unspecified
      Format: Blueprint
      Condition:Good
      Note:Townsend & Fleming
    - Topographic map, 1912 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 113
      Scale: 30'=1"
    - General plan of arrangement and planting, 1913 (Box 7)
      Sheet # 114
      Scale: 1/8"=1'
  - Acer, John H. A. Location: Grand Mere, Province du Quebec
    - General plan of arrangement and planting, 1913 (Box 20)
      Sheet # 515
    - Preliminary plan of arrangement and grading, 1912 (Box 20)
      Sheet # 516
      Scale: 1"=20'
      Condition:Fair
    - Stable - Front elevation, Undated (Box 70)
      Sheet # 1980
      Condition:Poor
    - Stable - Second floor plan, Undated (Box 70)
      Sheet # 1981
    - Stable - Ground floor plan, Undated (Box 70)
      Sheet # 1982
    - Interior elevation of dining room, Undated (Box 70)
      Sheet # 1983
      Scale: 1/4"=1'
    - Interior elevation - West wall billiard room, East elevation - Hall, Undated (Box 70)
      Sheet # 1984
    - Living room fire-place, Undated (Box 70)
      Sheet # 1985
    - East elevation, 1912 (Box 70)
      Sheet # 1986
    - North and South elevations, 1912 (Box 70)
      Sheet # 1987
    - West elevation, 1912 (Box 70)
      Sheet # 1988
    - Basement plan, 1912 (Box 70)
      Sheet # 1989
    - Ground floor plan, 1912 (Box 70)
      Sheet # 1990
    - Second floor plan, 1912 (Box 70)
      Sheet # 1991
    - Third floor plan, 1912 (Box 70)
      Sheet # 1992
  - Alexander, Esq., D. W. Location: Toronto, Ontario
    - Plan showing wall and landing platform, Undated (Box 14)
      Sheet # 278
      Scale: 1"=4'
      Format: Tracing paper
    - Sketch for terrace wall - service yard - garden gate and arch, Undated (Box 59)
      Sheet # 1678
  - Allen, Esq., Arthur Location: Glenview, Kentucky
    - Plan of Terrace Garden, Undated (Box 16)
      Sheet # 345
      Scale: 1/8"1'
    - Proposed site plan, 1913 (Folder 20)
      Sheet # 346
    - Proposed site plan, 1913 (Folder 21)
      Sheet # 347
    - View of service and entrance court walls, Undated (Box 16)
      Sheet # 348
    - Plan of arrangement, 1914 (Folder 20)
      Sheet # 349
    - Plan for site arrangement, 1914 (Folder 21)
      Sheet # 352
    - Plan for site arrangement, 1914 (Folder 21)
      Sheet # 353
    - Perspective of Garden showing possible treatment of Low brick garden wall, Undated (Box 17)
      Sheet # 354
    - Sketch plan of pool and terrace, Undated (Box 17)
      Sheet # 355
    - Entrance porch enclosure - Scheme "E" with blinds, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
      Sheet # 356
    - Entrance porch enclosure - Scheme "B" with glazed sash, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
      Sheet # 357
    - Entrance porch enclosure - Scheme "A" with glazed sash, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
      Sheet # 358
    - Entrance porch enclosure - Scheme "A" with blinds, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
      Sheet # 359
    - Perspective view of entrance porch, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
      Sheet # 360
    - Entrance porch enclosure - Scheme "C" with glazed sash, Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
      Sheet # 361
    - View of entrance court and service wall, Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
      Sheet # 362
    - Perspective of garden, Undated (Box 17)
      Sheet # 363
    - Sketch of lower head of garden, Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
      Sheet # 364
    - Sketch of gate post, likely, 1916 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      Sheet # 365
      Scale: 1"=1'
    - View of court walls from living terrace, Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
      Sheet # 366
    - Perspective of Garden, Undated (Box 9)
      Sheet # 367
      Format: Heavy Construction paper
    - Rear elevation of library pavilion, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      Sheet # 368
    - Library pavilion - elevation away from tennis court, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      Sheet # 369
    - Library pavilion - elevation toward tennis court, 1914 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      Sheet # 370
    - Perspective of house showing possible treatment of dining room façade, Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
      Sheet # 371
    - Sketch of terrace, Undated (Box 17)
      Sheet # 372
    - 1/4" scale elevations of court wall, Undated (Box 17)
      Sheet # 373
    - Library pavilion - Interior elevation looking away from court, 1914 (Box 9)
      Sheet # 374
    - Library pavilion - Front elevation, 1914 (Box 10)
      Sheet # 375
    - Library pavilion plan, 1914 (Box 10)
      Sheet # 376
    - Elevation of garden wall from lawn, Undated (Box 17)
      Sheet # 377
    - 1/8" scale elevation of main garden wall, Undated (Box 17)
      Sheet # 378
    - Elevation of main garden wall, Undated (Box 17)
      Sheet # 379
  - American Radiator Company Location: Buffalo, New York
    - Plan showing grading of grounds, 1910 (Folder 43a)
      Sheet # 1440
      Format: Linen
    - Sketch for arrangement of grounds, 1910 (Folder 43a)
      Sheet # 1441
    - Sketch for arrangement of grounds, 1910 (Box 43, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 1442
    - Planting sketch for surrounding of Lunch room at the Institute for Thermal Research, 1911 (Box 43, Folder 3)
      Sheet # 1443
    - Working sections, 1910 (Box 48)
      Sheet # 1444
      Scale: 1/2"=1'
    - Survey of the grounds, 1910 (Folder 44a)
      Sheet # 1445
      Scale: 1/10"=1'
    - Arrangement and planting of grounds, 1910 (Folder 44a)
      Sheet # 1446
      Note: Client listed as American Radiator Institute
    - Rough sketch, grounds, Undated (Folder 44a)
      Sheet # 1447
      Format: Manila paper
    - Floor plans, 1909 (Folder 44a)
      Sheet # 1448
    - Sketch for arrangement for grounds, 1910 (Folder 44a)
      Sheet # 1449
  - American Scenic & Historic Preservation Society, Letchworth Park Committee Location: Letchworth Park, New York
    - Perspective sketch of proposed bridge across Dehgayasoh Creek from bottom of main ravine, Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Sheet # 126
      Format: Tracing paper with crayon
    - No. 2 Perspective sketch of proposed bridge across Dehgayasoh Creek in Letchworth park, Undated (Box 7)
      Sheet # 127
    - Perspective sketch of proposed bridge across Dehgayasoh Creek from bottom of main ravine, Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Sheet # 128
    - Perspective sketch of one-arch bridge across Dehgayasoh Creek from bottom of main ravine, 1927 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Sheet # 129
    - No. 1 Perspective sketch of proposed bridge across Dehgayasoh Creek in Letchworth park, Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
      Sheet # 130
    - Proposed bridge across Dehgayasoh Creek, 1927 (Box 7)
      Sheet # 131
    - Single span bridge over Dehgayasoh Creek, 1927 (Box 7)
      Sheet # 132
  - Amherst Estates Location: Buffalo, New York
    - Site plan, Undated (Folder 51)
      Sheet # 1853
      Scale: 1"=300'
  - Andrews, M. Location: Cleveland, Ohio
    - Design for living hall fireplace, Undated (Box 35)
      Sheet # 970
    - Design for octagon mantel, 1917 (Box 35)
      Sheet # 971
    - Detail of living hall mantel, Undated (Box 35)
      Sheet # 972
    - Detail of octagon mantel, 1917 (Box 35)
      Sheet # 973
    - Details for vestibule glazed partition, 1918 (Box 35)
      Sheet # 974
    - Ground floor plan of cottage, 1917 (Box 35)
      Sheet # 975
    - Plan and section of cellar, 1917 (Box 22, Folder 5)
      Sheet # 976
      Scale: 1/2"=1';1/4"=1'
    - Entrance and service elevations, 1917 (Box 35)
      Sheet # 977
    - Woodland (Street) elevation, 1917 (Box 35)
      Sheet # 978
    - Grading measurements of road, likely, Undated (Box 35)
      Sheet # 981
      Format: Cardstock - Heavy paper, likely
  - Ashland Golf Club, likely Location: Fayette County, Kentucky
    - Contour map, 1936 (Folder 3)
      Sheet # 927
      Scale: 100'=1"
    - Contour map, 1936 (Folder 33)
      Sheet # 928
    - Tracing from contour map, 1936 (Folder 33)
      Sheet # 929
      Format: Vellum
    - Outline of contour plan, Undated (Folder 33)
      Sheet # 930
    - Outline of contour plan, Undated (Folder 33)
      Sheet # 931
  - Automobile Club of Buffalo Location: Unspecified
    - Description unspecified, Undated (Box 9)
      Sheet # 1562
    - Description unspecified, Undated (Box 10)
      Sheet # 1563
    - Description unspecified, Undated (Box 53)
      Sheet # 1598
    - The Triangle, Sketch, Undated (Box 53)
      Sheet # 1599
  - Location: Buffalo, New York
    - Club house, Undated (Box 53)
      Sheet # 1592
    - Sketch of clubhouse and grounds, Undated (Box 53)
      Sheet # 1595
    - Improvement of triangle at Genesee, Mohawk and Franklin streets (negative, likely), 1904 (Box 53)
      Sheet # 1596
      Format: Stock paper, Sepia
  - Buffalo (Survey for Driving Show) Location: Buffalo, likely
    - Triangle at Genesee, Mohawk and Franklin streets (two drawings with same number- Triangle but this one is in Box 49, Folder 5), 1903 (Box 49, Folder 5)
      Sheet # 1553
    - Improvement of triangle at intersection of Niagara, Morgan and Mohawk streets, 1906 (Box 49, Folder 5)
      Sheet # 1556
      Scale: 1"=10'
  - Location: Clarence, New York
    - Plan showing house and arrangement of grounds, 1910 (Box 59)
      Sheet # 1679
    - Plan showing location of house and arrangement of grounds, Undated (Folder 50)
      Sheet # 1806
      Scale: 1"=50'
    - Club House - First floor plan, 1910 (Box 62)
      Sheet # 1814
      Note:By Esenwein & Johnson
    - Club House - Foundation plan, 1910 (Box 62)
      Sheet # 1815
    - Club House - Second floor plan, 1910 (Box 62)
      Sheet # 1816
    - Club House - Side elevation, 1910 (Box 62)
      Sheet # 1817
      Condition:Poor to Fair
    - Club House - End elevation, 1910 (Box 62)
      Sheet # 1818
    - Arrangement about Club House, 1910 (Box 63)
      Sheet # 1819
    - Plan of garden and fore-court, 1910 (Box 63)
      Sheet # 1820
    - Survey and levels, 1910 (Box 63)
      Sheet # 1821
    - General plan, 1910 (Box 63)
      Sheet # 1822
      Scale: 1"=40'
    - Rough sketch of Club House grounds, Undated (Box 63)
      Sheet # 1823
    - General Plan, 1910 (Box 63)
      Sheet # 1824
    - Survey and levels, 1910 (Box 63)
      Sheet # 1825
  - Babcock, F. R. Location: Valencia, Pennsylvania
    - Sketch plan of arrangement, 1916 (Folder 39)
      Sheet # 1148
      Format: Tracing paper with Crayon
    - Sketch plan of arrangement, Undated (Folder 39)
      Sheet # 1149
      Format: Crayon and pencil on Tracing paper
  - Briar Hill School Location: Fayette county, Kentucky
    - Construction details, 1933 (Box 31)
      Sheet # 783
      Note:By Architect Hugh Meriwether
    - Construction details, 1934 (Box 31)
      Sheet # 784
    - Alternate main entrance details, 1934 (Box 31)
      Sheet # 785
    - Cross sections of the school property, Undated (Box 31)
      Sheet # 786
    - Cross sections of the school property, Undated (Box 31)
      Sheet # 787
    - Topographical survey of property, Undated (Box 31)
      Sheet # 788
      Scale: 1"=30'
    - General landscape plan, 1936 (Folder 30)
      Sheet # 789
      Scale: 1/16"=1'
      Format: Mylar
    - Topographic map, 1936 (Folder 30)
      Sheet # 790
    - Details - Steps, walls and fences, Undated (Folder 30)
      Sheet # 791
    - Sketch of site arrangement, Undated (Box 31)
      Sheet # 792
    - Rough sketch of arrangement, Undated (Box 31)
      Sheet # 793
    - Sketch plan and elevation of school property, Undated (Box 31)
      Sheet # 794
    - Sketch plan of entry to school property, Undated (Folder 30)
      Sheet # 795
    - Preliminary landscape plan, Undated (Folder 30)
      Sheet # 796
    - Preliminary plan and elevations of entry to school, Undated (Folder 30)
      Sheet # 797
  - Briggs, Charles E Location: Euclid Heights, Cleveland, Ohio
    - Garden details, 1917 (Folder 29)
      Sheet # 727
    - Garden details, 1917 (Folder 29)
      Sheet # 728
      Scale: 1/16="1'; 1/2"=1'
    - Sketches for playhouse, Undated (Folder 29)
      Sheet # 729
    - Detail of motif - "U", Undated (Folder 31)
      Sheet # 798
      Scale: 1/2"=1'; 1"=1'
    - Detail of motif - "U", Undated (Folder 31)
      Sheet # 799
    - East and south elevations - Playhouse, Undated (Box 31)
      Sheet # 800
    - East and sections of fireplace for playhouse, 1917 (Box 31)
      Sheet # 801
    - Plan for playhouse, 1920 (Box 31)
      Sheet # 802
    - Ceiling plan showing beam construction - Playhouse, 1917 (Box 31)
      Sheet # 803
    - North and west elevations - Playhouse, Undated (Box 31)
      Sheet # 804
    - East and south elevations - Playhouse, Undated (Box 31)
      Sheet # 805
    - Elevations of interiors of Playhouse, Undated (Box 31)
      Sheet # 806
    - Detail of door, Undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
      Sheet # 807
    - Elevation of crenellated wall, 1917 (Box 32)
      Sheet # 808
    - Court yard pool detail, 1917 (Box 32)
      Sheet # 809
    - Plan of Playhouse, Undated (Box 32)
      Sheet # 810
    - Wall "A" at Service court, Undated (Box 32)
      Sheet # 811
    - Fireplace for Playhouse, 1917 (Box 32)
      Sheet # 812
    - Second floor and roof plan of Playhouse, 1917 (Box 32)
      Sheet # 813
    - North and west elevations - Playhouse, Undated (Box 32)
      Sheet # 814
    - Ceiling plan - Playhouse, 1917 (Box 32)
      Sheet # 815
    - Dovecote - details, 1917 (Folder 31)
      Sheet # 816
      Scale: 1 1/2"=1'
    - Garden details, Undated (Folder 31)
      Sheet # 817
      Scale: 1/2"=1'; 1/4"=1'
    - Garden details, Undated (Folder 31)
      Sheet # 818
    - General arrangement plan, 1917 (Folder 31)
      Sheet # 819
    - Revised trench plan for Greenhouse, 1919 (Box 32)
      Sheet # 820
      Note: By Lord and Burnham Company
    - Revised plan for pool and surroundings, Undated (Box 32)
      Sheet # 821
    - Swimming pool details, 1919 (Box 32)
      Sheet # 822
    - Sketch - Interior of wall with Fleming's comments on back, Undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
      Sheet # 823
    - Second floor plan and Roof plan, 1917 (Box 32)
      Sheet # 824
    - Detail of Garage court wall, Undated (Box 32)
      Sheet # 825
    - Sections and plans of roof, 1919 (Box 32)
      Sheet # 826
      Note:By King Construction Company
    - Masonry plan, 1919 (Box 32)
      Sheet # 827
      Note:By Lord and Burnham Company
    - Plan of Sewer and water lines, service and garden extensions, 1919 (Box 32)
      Sheet # 828
    - Final plan of arrangement, 1918 (Folder 32)
      Sheet # 829
      Condition:Fair, oversized
    - Dovecote - plan and elevations, etc., 1917 (Folder 32)
      Sheet # 830
    - Swimming pool details, Undated (Folder 32)
      Sheet # 831
    - General plan of a re-filtration plant for a swimming pool, Undated (Folder 32)
      Sheet # 832
      Note:By The New York Continental Jewell Filtration Company
    - First floor plan - pool, garden and service buildings, Group, 1919 (Folder 32)
      Sheet # 833
    - Miscellaneous details - plan of flower garden, 1917 (Folder 33)
      Sheet # 834
      Scale: 1/4"=1'; 1/2"=1'
    - Garden details, 1917 (Folder 33)
      Sheet # 835
    - General arrangement plan, Undated (Folder 33)
      Sheet # 836
  - Buffalo/Buffalo City Park Location: Buffalo, New York
    - Streets near Erie basin, Undated (Folder 48)
      Sheet # 1627
    - Street layout, Undated (Folder 48)
      Sheet # 1628
  - Buffalo Park Commission Location: Buffalo, New York
    - Delaware Park - proposed site for "David" statue, Undated (Folder 51)
      Sheet # 1518
    - Triangle at Erie and Franklin streets (No. 41-9), 1905 (Folder 51)
      Sheet # 1519
    - Plan for the improvement of triangle at Genesee, Mohawk and Franklin streets, 1904 (Folder 51)
      Sheet # 1520
    - Plan for the improvement of triangle at Genesee, Mohawk and Franklin streets, 1904 (Folder 51)
      Sheet # 1521
    - Triangle, Undated (Folder 51)
      Sheet # 1522
    - Improvement of triangle at Genesee, Mohawk and Franklin streets, 1904 (Folder 51)
      Sheet # 1523
    - Triangle, Undated (Box 49, Folder 2)
      Sheet # 1524
    - Improvement of triangle at Genesee, Mohawk and Franklin streets, 1906 (Box 49, Folder 2)
      Sheet # 1525
    - Triangle, Undated (Box 49, Folder 2)
      Sheet # 1526
    - Protection of Elm tree at Swan and Pearl Streets, 1905 (Box 49, Folder 2)
      Sheet # 1527
    - Triangle at Erie and Franklin streets, 1905 (Box 49, Folder 2)
      Sheet # 1528
    - Triangle, Undated (Box 49, Folder 2)
      Sheet # 1529
    - Triangle, Undated (Box 49, Folder 2)
      Sheet # 1530
    - Triangle, Undated (Box 49, Folder 2)
      Sheet # 1531
    - Improvement of triangle at intersection of Niagara, Morgan and Mohawk streets, 1906 (Box 49, Folder 2)
      Sheet # 1532
    - Sketch for coping, Undated (Box 49, Folder 2)
      Sheet # 1533
  - Burns, Henry Location: Unspecified
    - Second floor plan; Revised house and grounds, 1922 (Folder 49)
      Sheet # 1691
      Scale: 1/8"=1'; 1"=20'
      Format: Blue
    - First floor plan; Revised first floor plan, Undated (Folder 49)
      Sheet # 1692
    - Revised sketch of elevations, 1922 (Box 60)
      Sheet # 1697
    - Residence(revised), 1922 (Box 60)
      Sheet # 1698
    - Residence, Undated (Box 60)
      Sheet # 1699
    - Second floor plan; sketch of elevation, Undated (Box 60)
      Sheet # 1700
    - Residence, Undated (Box 60)
      Sheet # 1701
    - First floor plan, Undated (Box 60)
      Sheet # 1703
    - First floor plan (revised), Undated (Box 60)
      Sheet # 1704
    - Second floor plan, Undated (Box 60)
      Sheet # 1705
    - Second floor plan (revised), Undated (Box 60)
      Sheet # 1706
    - Sketch elevation, Undated (Box 60)
      Sheet # 1707
    - Second floor plan, Undated (Box 60)
      Sheet # 1708
    - Sketch elevation (revised), Undated (Box 60)
      Sheet # 1709
    - First floor plan, Undated (Box 60)
      Sheet # 1710
    - Planting plan, Undated (Folder 51)
      Sheet # 1852
      Format: Stock paper
  - Location: Grosse Pointe Farms, Michigan
    - Lot owned by Henry, 1922 (Box 61)
      Sheet # 1799
  - Caldwell, Rogers C. Location: Nashville, Tennessee
    - Perspective sketch for wall and garden treatment at rock outcrop, south of residence, 1929 (Box 58)
      Sheet # 1662
      Format: Tracing paper, Colored
  - Carnegie, Andrew Location: Shadowbrook, Lenox, Massachusetts (or unspecified)
    - Survey rider, 1917 (Box 45)
      Sheet # 1260
    - Topo, 1917 (Folder 41)
      Sheet # 1262
    - Detail of steps, file no. 365, Undated (Box 45)
      Sheet # 1263
    - Steps to rose garden, Undated (Box 45)
      Sheet # 1264
      Scale: 3/4"=1'
    - Detail of garden steps, file no. 365, plan no. 13, Undated (Box 45)
      Sheet # 1265
    - Pool plumbing and fittings, Undated (Folder 41)
      Sheet # 1261
    - Pool plumbing and fittings, 1917 (Box 45)
      Sheet # 1266
    - Garden Plan, likely, Undated (Box 45)
      Sheet # 1267
    - Garden Plan, Undated (Box 45)
      Sheet # 1268
    - Garden Plan, Undated (Box 45)
      Sheet # 1269
    - Profile, Path about pool, Undated (Box 45)
      Sheet # 1270
    - Pool plumbing and fittings, 1917 (Box 45)
      Sheet # 1271
    - Rough sketch, pool / Grotto, Undated (Box 45)
      Sheet # 1272
    - Outline sketch, Plumbing / Pool, Undated (Box 45)
      Sheet # 1273
    - Garden Plan, Undated (Box 45)
      Sheet # 1274
    - Detail of steps to pool path, 1918 (Folder 41)
      Sheet # 1275
    - Map of property, 1917 (Folder 41)
      Sheet # 1276
    - Pool lighting, 1917 (Box 45)
      Sheet # 1277
    - Pool lighting, 1917 (Box 43, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 1278
    - Steps, Terrace to lawn (void), 1917 (Folder 41)
      Sheet # 1279
    - Shadow brook, Estate of Shotter, 1907 (Folder 41)
      Sheet # 1280
      Scale: 1"=100'
    - Upper gardens, 1917 (Folder 41)
      Sheet # 1281
    - Steps to pool path, 1917 (Box 45)
      Sheet # 1282
    - Elevation, steps to rose garden, Undated (Box 45)
      Sheet # 1283
    - Sketch, Garden scene, Undated (Box 10)
      Sheet # 1284
      Format: Colored pencil on Tracing paper
    - Sketch, Garden scene, Undated (Box 10)
      Sheet # 1285
    - Alterations, first floor plan, 1917 (Box 10)
      Sheet # 1286
      Scale: 1/8"=3'
    - Alterations, second floor plan, 1917 (Box 10)
      Sheet # 1287
    - Alterations, third floor plan, 1917 (Box 10)
      Sheet # 1288
    - Outlines, Undated (Box 45)
      Sheet # 1289
    - Steps to rose garden, 1917 (Box 45)
      Sheet # 1290
    - Steps to rose garden, Undated (Box 45)
      Sheet # 1291
    - Steps to rose garden, Undated (Box 45)
      Sheet # 1292
    - Steps to rose garden, Undated (Box 45)
      Sheet # 1293
    - Sketch of garden structure, Undated (Box 43, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 1294
    - Sketch of garden, Undated (Box 43, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 1295
    - Sketch of garden, Undated (Box 43, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 1296
    - Sketch of garden structure, Undated (Box 43, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 1297
    - Sketch of garden, Undated (Box 43, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 1298
    - Sketch of garden, Undated (Box 43, Folder 1)
      Sheet # 1299
    - Steps, terrace to lawn - service end, 1917 (Box 59)
      Sheet # 1680
    - Sketch plan of arrangement of lower garden (Folder 54)
      Sheet # 1711
      Scale: About 1"=40' or 50'
  - Carrier, Robert M. Location: Louisville, Kentucky
    - Planting plan of the garden, 1913 (Folder 10)